Planned Parenthood Federation of America Records (PPFA II): SERIES V. Affiliates, 1930-80 (Part 2)
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. AFFILIATES (PART 2)
  - Connecticut
    - New Haven
      - Affiliation, PP Correspondence from 1957
        - 1957-1974 (Box 185, Folder 19)
        - 1975-1980 (Box 185)
      - Affiliation, PP League, 1967-1972 (Box 185, Folder 20)
      - PP League of Connecticut from 1973
        - 1973-1974 (Box 185, Folder 21)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 185)
      - PP Chapter, 1962-1966 (Box 185, Folder 22)
      - PP League, 1964-1967 (Box 185, Folder 23)
      - PP League of Connecticut, Chapters
        - 1974 (Box 185, Folder 24)
        - 1975-1979 (Box 185)
      - PP League, Benefit, 10/21/1973 (Box 185, Folder 25)
    - 1961-1965 (Box 185, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1961 (Box 185, Folder 27)
    - 1959 (Box 185, Folder 28)
    - Newspaper Articles Connecticut, 1960 (Box 185, Folder 29)
    - Newspapers, 1961-1965 (Box 185, Folder 30-33)
  - Planned Parenthood, World Population Inter-Regional Statistical Report (2 copies), 1970 (Box 185, Folder 34a-b)
  - Planned Parenthood World Population Inter-Regional Statistical Report: Patient Statistics (2 copies), 1969 (Box 185, Folder 35a-b)
  - Manual for Regional Offices, 1968-1970 (Box 185, Folder 36)
  - History (of the Regions), 1963-1973 (Box 185, Folder 37)
  - History (of the Regions), 1975 (Box 185, Folder 38)
  - E & P: Sub-Committee on Organization for History, 1972 (Box 185, Folder 39)
  - Regional, General, Area Director/Assistant Area Director, Applicants, 1977 (Box 185, Folder 40)
  - Regional, General, Area Offices (Blaise Memo 8/11/77), 1977 (Box 185, Folder 41)
  - Series V, Due to it's large size, the SERIES V container list is divided into two parts. Go to Part 1.